Inventory of the Herbert H. Bateman Papers, 1946-1982, 1968-1982
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Bateman's Pocket Appointment Books, 1964-1977. (Box-folder 22:3-9)
  - Bateman's pocket "Lawyer's Diaries" (appointment books), 1964-1965., 2 items. (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Bateman's pocket appointment books, 1966-1967., 3 items. (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Bateman's pocket appointment books, 1968-1969., 2 items. (Box-folder 22:5)
  - Bateman's pocket appointment books, 1970-1971., 2 items. (Box-folder 22:6)
  - Bateman's pocket appointment books, 1972-1973., 2 items. (Box-folder 22:7)
  - Bateman's pocket appointment books, 1974-1975., 3 items. (Box-folder 22:8)
  - Bateman's pocket appointment books, 1976-1977., 3 items. (Box-folder 22:9)
  Series 248: Photograph
- Photograph and cover letter, ca. 1971., 2 items. Photographic Print. Black and White. Glossy. (Box-folder 22:10)
  Photograph of closet door of dormitory room at the College of William and Mary, showing "The official Room 205 s--t-list," with Bateman's picture appearing at the top. Bateman was then sponsoring a Senate Joint Resolution to prohibit "open" visitation in state college dormitories. Photograph and cover letter was taken from the William and Mary, the College of (W&M) series (Box-folder: 20:10).
  Series 249: Oversize and Medium Oversize Maps
- Oversize and Medium Oversize Maps, 1969-1976, n.d. (Box 22)
  All maps were removed from the reapportionment series except the finial map, which was removed from the ports of Virginia series.
  - Census tract map of City of Newport News, Virginia, revised 9 June 1970., 1 item. (Box 22)
  - Census tract map of the City of Newport News, Virginia, marked in ink with population [?] calculations in margins, n.d., 1 item. Reduced version of map in oversize file. (Box 22)
  - Census tract map of City of Newport News, Virginia, with ink markings and cross-hatching and population [?] calculations of "NN districts" in left margin, n.d., 1 item. (Box 22)
  - Census tract map of City of Newport News, Virginia, with ink markings and numbers drawn on map, and population [?] figures in left margin, n.d., 1 item. (Box 22)
  - Map of James City and York counties, Virginia showing primary and secondary highways, prepared by the [Virginia] Department of Highways, 1 January 1969., 1 item. (Box 22)
  - Map of James City and York counties, Virginia showing primary and secondary highways, prepared by the [Virginia] Department of Highways, with portion colored in purple ink, 1 January 1969., 1 item. (Box 22)
  - Map of James City and York counties, Virginia, showing primary and secondary highways, prepared by the [Virginia] Department of Highways, with portion colored in green ink, 1 January 1969., 1 item. (Box 22)
  - Map of James City and York counties, Virginia, showing primary and secondary highways, prepared by [Virginia] Department of Highways, with portions colored in purple and green ink, 1 January 1969., 1 item. (Box 22)
  - Map of Fort Eustis, Newport News, Virginia, drafted by U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, 20 August 1969., 1 item. (Box 22)
  - Map of Fort Eustis, Newport News, Virginia, prepared by U.S. Army Corps of Engineers, June 1969., 1 item. (Box 22)
  - Map of subdivision plat of "Greenfield," Isle of Wight County, Virginia, prepared by John N. Ruth, of Hampton, Virginia, scale 1" = 100', 19 June 1976., 1 item. (Box 22)